<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://carobot.org/carobot.org/blog</id>
    <title>Carobot Learning and Research Organization Blog</title>
    <updated>2021-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://carobot.org/carobot.org/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Carobot Learning and Research Organization Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://carobot.org/carobot.org/img/carobot.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the CaroBlog!]]></title>
        <id>https://carobot.org/carobot.org/blog/welcome</id>
        <link href="https://carobot.org/carobot.org/blog/welcome"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to the Carobot Learning and Research Organization's blog! We are thrilled to have you here. Our blog is dedicated to sharing insightful articles, tutorials, and stories that ignite curiosity and foster a love for STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics).]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello and welcome to the Carobot Learning and Research Organization's blog! We are thrilled to have you here. Our blog is dedicated to sharing insightful articles, tutorials, and stories that ignite curiosity and foster a love for STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics).</p>
<p>At Carobot, our mission is to make STEM education accessible and engaging for everyone. Whether you are a student, educator, parent, or simply someone passionate about learning, you'll find a wealth of resources here to inspire and support your journey in STEM.</p>
<p>What You Can Expect from Our Blog:</p>
<ul>
<li><b>In-Depth Tutorials:</b> Step-by-step guides and tutorials on various STEM topics, from robotics and coding to engineering and scientific experiments.</li>
<li><b>Educational Resources:</b> Access a variety of resources, including project ideas, lesson plans, and educational tools.
Community Highlights: Discover the amazing work being done by our community members and learn how you can get involved.</li>
</ul>
<p>Thank you for visiting the Carobot Learning and Research Blog. We hope you find our content both informative and inspiring. Together, let's explore the wonders of STEM and make learning an exciting adventure!</p>
<p>Happy learning!</p>
<p>The Carobot Team</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Salonga</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/maria-salonga-b89385248/</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Green</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/graham-a-m-green/</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Jacky Lau</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/jackykklau/</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="Announcement" term="Announcement"/>
        <category label="STEM" term="STEM"/>
        <category label="Outreach" term="Outreach"/>
    </entry>
</feed>